The most ruthless Robinson of all time!
Black Tuesday is a crime, thriller film directed by Hugo Fregonese.
Vicious gangster Vincent Canelli pulls off a daring prison escape just moments before going to the electric
chair, taking with him Peter Manning – a bank robber and cop killer who was to die right after him.
Taking several hostages along, they try to get their hands on the loot from
Manning’s robbery to finance their escape from the country.
Vincent Canelli, played by Edward G. Robinson.
Hatti Combest, played by Jean Parker.
Peter Manning, played by Peter Graves.
Father Slocum, played by Milburn Stone.
Joey Stewart, played by Warren Stevens.
Ellen Norris, played by Sylvia Findley.
Black Tuesday is a 1954 American crime drama film noir
directed by Hugo Fregonese and starring Edward G.
Robinson, Peter Graves and Jean Parker.
The supporting cast features Milburn Stone, Warren
Stevens, Jack Kelly and Russell Johnson.
The film explores themes of death row, prison
escape, escaped convict, film noir.
The tone is dark and intense.